Marielle PIERRE-VICTOR

CREATIVE TECHNOLOGIST

I believe imagination and storytelling impact people in the greatest way. I have always dreamt of using technology to add magic and reality to the dreams. I have worked in quality in one of my world, I have studied electronic in school, and been an electrical safety technician. I have also performed dance shows and today I want to merge all my experiences and passions in a logical sequence.

CAPABILITY



Learning

Detail-oriented

Teaching

Quality

Electrical safety

EDUCATION



2011 - 2012 MANCHESTER METROPOLITAN UNIVERSITY

Msc Electronic Engineering,

2008-2009 UNIVERSITY OF GLAMORGAN

 Beng Electronic and Communication Engineering

CONTACT



- 07 82 40 26 88
- m.pierrevictor@gmail.com
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/marielle -pierre-victor-8065415b/ 4 rue st just 95190 Goussainville
- 4 rue st just 95190 Goussainville (with family member at 32 promenade du belvédère 77200 TORCY)

EXPERIENCE



2022

 Community teacher - Teaching French on Italki

2017-2021

 Safety technician - LCIE Bureau
 Veritas: electrical safety testing according to standards

2014-2017

Quality technician - DAHER SACATA
 Visual and documentary inspection
 following internal procedures